this is Nick with logos by Nick comm and
我是尼克·康姆的标志尼克
in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can use a drawing tablet with
如何将绘图板与
Inkscape and if you'd like to learn more
Inkscape和如果您想了解更多
about how Inkscape works be sure to
关于Inkscape的工作原理，请务必
check out my Inkscape masterclass it's a
看看我的Inkscape大师课，它是一个
collection of over 50 videos where I go
收集了50多个我去过的地方的视频
over every single tool and feature in
中的每一项工具和功能
Inkscape and I explain what it is and
Inkscape和我解释了它是什么
demonstrate how it works I'll have a
演示一下它是如何工作的，我会有一个
link in the description of the video if
视频描述中的链接，如果
you want to check that out so to get us
你想去查一下吗？这样我们就能
started here as you can see I have
从这里开始，正如你所看到的，我有
Inkscape opened up on my screen and I
Inkscape在我的屏幕上打开，我
have my drawing tablet here on my desk
把我的绘图板放在桌子上
and the way that a drawing tablet works
以及绘图板的工作方式
is that it basically allows you to
它基本上允许你
create freehand digital art the same way
以同样的方式创作写意数字艺术
you would with the pencil and paper and
你会用铅笔和纸
the tablet I'm using here is a Wacom
我在这里使用的平板电脑是Wacom
Intuos I'll have a link in the
Intuos我会在
description to a short review I wrote
对我写的一篇简短评论的描述
about it last year in case you're
去年的事，以防你
interested the way that this works is
感兴趣的是它的工作方式是
that you plug it in through a USB Drive
你可以通过USB驱动器将其插入
and if you're using Windows 10 it should
如果你使用的是Windows 10，它应该
be automatically recognized and
被自动识别并
functional without having to install
功能正常，无需安装
anything that was the case for me anyway
无论如何，任何对我来说都是这样的事情
if that doesn't work for you then you'll
如果这对你不起作用，那么你将
probably have to install some drivers
可能需要安装一些驱动程序
depending on your operating system I'll
根据您的操作系统，我将
have a link in the description for those
在描述中有关于这些的链接
as well if you need to download them and
如果您需要下载它们，并且
once you have your tablet installed it
一旦你安装了平板电脑
basically functions the same way a mouse
基本上与鼠标的功能相同
would let me show you what I mean here
让我向你们展示我在这里的意思
I'm gonna take the tip of the pen and
我要拿起笔尖
hover it above the surface of the tablet
将其悬停在平板电脑表面上方
right here and if you notice as I move
就在这里，如果你注意到我移动的话
it around it moves the cursor on this
它在它周围移动光标在这个上面
screen as well and if you notice I'm not
屏幕也一样，如果你注意到我没有
actually touching the surface of a
实际接触到的是一个
tablet once I do touch the surface of
一旦我接触到了平板电脑的表面
the tablet it registers the same way it
它以同样的方式注册的平板电脑
would is if you were to click and drag
就是如果你点击并拖动
with your mouse and by the way this
用你的鼠标，顺便说一句
works system-wide you don't just have to
在整个系统范围内工作，您不仅需要
install this with Inkscape once you have
一旦您有了Inkscape，就将其与Inkscape一起安装
this installed you can use this with any
安装此程序后，您可以将此程序与任何
of your other applications as well so
您的其他应用程序也是如此
this this works it's kind of like
这个这个行得通，有点像
installing fonts where once it's
在哪里安装字体，一旦它
installed it works it works system-wide
安装后即可在整个系统范围内工作
and the way that this works here is that
而这里的运作方式是
the surface area of the tablet is
药片的表面积为
represented by the perimeter of your
由您的
screen so if you bring your if you bring
所以如果你带着你的如果你带着
the pen to the top left portion of the
的左上角的钢笔。
tablet the cursor is located in the top
Tablet光标位于顶部
left portion of the screen and then down
屏幕的左侧，然后向下
here to the bottom right so on and so
从这里到右下角，如此等等
forth you get the idea now once you have
第四，一旦你有了，你现在就有了想法
your tablet installed I would recommend
我建议您安装您的平板电脑
that you go through some of the settings
你需要经过一些设置
and get them set up first so what you're
先把它们设置好，所以你要做什么
wrong what you're gonna want to do is
错误的是你想要做的是
come over here to where it says search
过来，到上面写着搜索的地方来
and type in Wacom you're looking for a
然后在Wacom中输入您要查找的
Wacom tablet property
Wacom平板电脑物业
you click on that and over here you can
你点击它，在这里你可以
just take these buttons on the tablet
把这些按钮放在平板电脑上就行了
and program and to do whatever you want
编程，做任何你想做的事
these are these buttons over here I
这些是我这里的按钮
don't use them personally but if you
不要私下使用它们，但如果您
want to you can program that to whatever
想要什么，你可以编程成任何东西
you want what I'm paying attention to
你想要我关注的东西
mostly is the pen and mapping so first
大部分是笔和地图，所以才是第一
of all with the pen you can adjust the
最重要的是，使用钢笔可以调整
sensitivity to the pen or the distance
对笔或距离的敏感性
between the pen and a tablet with these
在笔和平板电脑之间有这些
settings over here over here you'll
设置在这里，在这里您将
notice you can program the buttons on
请注意，您可以对按钮进行编程
the pen if you look at the pen closely I
这支笔如果你仔细看这支笔的话
don't know if you can tell in the video
不知道你在视频里能不能看出来
but there's two buttons on this pen here
但是这支笔上有两个按钮
there's one down here and one up here
这里有一个，这里也有一个
and you can program these buttons to do
你可以对这些按钮进行编程来做
whatever you want if you click this drop
任何你想要的东西，如果你点击这个拖放
down over here you can see all the
在这里你可以看到所有的
different things you could program it to
不同的东西，你可以给它编程
do I programmed it to do a specific
我是不是编程让它做一个特定的
keystroke which is control Z which is
按键，即控制Z，它是
the undo function and I find that useful
Undo功能，我发现它很有用
because sometimes I'll be drawing
因为有时候我会画画
brushstrokes or something and I don't
笔触或其他什么东西，我不会
like how it came out
就像它是怎么出来的
instead of having to come over to the
而不是不得不来到
keyboard and press control Z I can just
键盘上按下Ctrl Z就可以了
press that button on the pen and undo
按下笔上那个按钮，然后撤消
that brushstroke so that's really useful
那一笔，真的很有用
and the other thing over here disabled
这里的另一件事是残废的
this other button I haven't found a use
这另一个按钮我还没找到用处
for it yet so like I just left it
因为它就像我刚刚离开它一样
disabled and then finally over here
残废了，最后到了这里
where it says mapping this is
它所说的地图就是
particularly important if you're using
特别重要的是，如果您使用
multiple monitors like I am as you can
像我这样的多个显示器，就像你一样
see here I have a triple monitor setup
请看这里，我有一个三重显示器设置
but I have it set up so that this tablet
但我已经把它设置好了，所以这块平板电脑
only works on this Center monitor right
只能在此中心显示器上正常工作
here which is the monitor I'm using for
这就是我要用的显示器
this video
这段视频
by default when I first installed when I
默认情况下，当我第一次安装时
first installed this tablet when I first
我第一次安装这款平板电脑的时候
plugged it in it had all three monitors
插上电源后，它有三个显示器
indicated here so that when I used the
在此指示，以便在我使用
surface area of the tablet this whole
整个药片的表面积
width of the tablet represented the
图形输入板的宽度表示
entire width of all three of these
所有这三个区域的整个宽度
monitors but the height stayed the same
监视器，但高度保持不变
this created a distortion of an aspect
这造成了一个方面的扭曲
ratio of three to one and it was really
三比一，这真的是
difficult to draw I couldn't figure out
很难画，我想不通
why things that I was drawing with the
为什么我画的东西
tablet didn't look right on the screen
平板电脑在屏幕上看起来不对劲
like for example if you were to draw a
例如，如果您要绘制一个
perfectly round circle on the tablet it
平板电脑上完美的圆圈吧
would be represented by a really
将由一个真正的
elongated ellipse on the screen here and
屏幕上的细长椭圆形
I couldn't figure out why that was and
我想不出为什么会这样
then eventually I realized it was
然后我终于意识到这是
because I had I had the surface area of
因为我有我有的表面积
the tablet mapped to all three monitors
平板电脑映射到了所有三个显示器
so if you're using multiple monitors
因此，如果您使用多个监视器
make sure to come over here to the to
一定要到TO这里来
the mapping tab and just set it up so
映射选项卡，然后将其设置为
you're just using one monitor here then
那么，您在这里只使用了一个监视器
we can close out of that and now we're
我们可以关闭它，而现在我们
good to get started here in Inkscape
很高兴在Inkscape这里开始
there's a few different things you can
你可以做几件不同的事情
do with the drawing tablet here in
在这里使用绘图板
Inkscape one thing you can do is you can
Inkscape你能做的一件事就是
come over here to the free hand lines
到这里来，到自由手线上来
tool the tutorial I did the other day
使用我前几天做的教程
about using custom brushes you can use
关于使用可以使用的自定义画笔
that another thing you could do is you
你可以做的另一件事是你自己
can create some calligraphy with the
可以用来创作一些书法
calligraphy pen over here for this I
这里有一支书法笔，这是我
like to use the dip pen the width I have
我想用我有的宽度的蘸笔
set to 37 the thinning set to 10 and
设置为37，细化设置为10，然后
then the rest the defaults are just the
那么其余的缺省值只是
default as they are and then you just
默认情况下，然后你就
come over to your canvas over here to
走到你的画布上来
your drawing tablet and then just click
您的绘图板，然后只需点击
and drag like that or actually press
像这样拖动或实际按下
down the pen and move it around to
把笔放下，把它移来移去
create some calligraphy like that and as
创作一些这样的书法，就像
you can see it draws it on the screen so
你可以看到它画在屏幕上，所以
that's one thing you can do with the
这是您可以使用
drawing tablet in Inkscape another thing
在Inkscape中绘制平板电脑是另一回事
this would be useful for is if you're
这将对IS有用，如果您
creating those line art style logos that
创建那些线条艺术风格的徽标
I did in the previous tutorial a couple
在上一个教程中，我做了几个
years ago it would be really useful for
几年前，它会对
that sort of thing is where you could
这类事情就是你可以
just draw them freehand without having
只要用手画就行了，不用
to do all of that with the with the
要完成所有这些任务，请使用
mouse and clicking and dragging so I
鼠标，然后点击并拖动，这样我
think that should do it for this
我觉得这样就够了
tutorial that's how you can go about
教程，这就是你可以如何去做
getting yourself set up with a drawing
为自己设置一个图形
tablet and Inkscape if you have any
平板电脑和Inkscape(如果您有
questions leave a comment below and as
问题请在下面留下评论，并作为
always thanks for watching
永远感谢您的收看
you
你